Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
We live in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We'll live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Luffy!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
I have terrible news!
A dinosaur ate Nami!
What in a way?
We were running through the jungle
to get away from the dinosaur,
and then suddenly I turned around and
she was gone and must have gotten her.
I got my friend killed.
How can I live with myself now?
Hey, you guys, calm down.
Just listen to me for a second, will you?
If she was there one
moment and gone the next,
then you can't know for sure
what happened. Well, no.
It's not like it could stop and check.
I would have been eaten, too.
It was either a dinosaur
or some other wild beast.
What else could it possibly be?
I don't know for sure.
But if Baroque Works followed
us from Whiskey Peak,
it would make sense for them
to capture Nami and not you.
I think we may be in great
danger. We should go.
You mean that Baroque Works
is here on the island with us?
Wait.
But why capture Nami and not me?
Because you haven't gotten in their way.
Most likely you aren't on
their assassination list.
Oh, okay.
Now that I think about it,
I bet that booby-trapped alcohol
was meant to get us instead.
Huh? Huh?
What did you say about alcohol?
Broggy gave Dory some of your alcohol
that must have been tampered with,
because when Dory drank
the barrels, they exploded.
No way!
They actually exploded inside the guy?
Wait, he was injured that badly
and he still ran off to go fight?
I tried to stop him and that's
how I ended up like this.
This is horrible!
Those two have been fighting as hard
as they can for a hundred years,
and they always ended in a draw.
Plus, their duels are fought with the
most honor and pride in the whole world!
Yeah.
There's no way they can settle
it once and for all like this!
Ah! Ah!
Get him!
Well, he keeps fighting.
Hmm.
He certainly is stubborn,
that Dory the Blue Ogre.
Yes, well, I should lend some assistance.
A whole century.
This has been a long and
difficult battle indeed.
I now know that this was a judgment.
A judgment from Elbath, the god of war.
I didn't have the god's protection.
And that is all.
Stop it, Luffy! Calm down.
Who was it?
Who did that?
Hey, Mr. Three.
I think I heard something.
Some pathetic animal yelping
helplessly in the jungle. Amusing.
Oh, these fights,
73, 467 duels,
73, 466 draws,
and one win
do
I
see tears of joy?
I doubt that happiness will last long!
But for now I offer
you my congratulations.
Did you say happiness?
You know nothing!
Who are you little man? I am Mr. Three.
That's a code name of course which
is necessary in my line of work.
I am an artist of sorts
and this is my assistant.
All the best artists
require assistance you see.
Her name
is Miss Goldenweed.
I tell you all this because I've already
caught you in one of my artworks.
What?
What have you done to me?
Right, Luffy.
I don't know what we're dealing with here,
but I'm gonna take care of them myself.
I'll come too, Usopp. Good.
Having you along with
me will be reassuring.
You're not going anywhere.
You guys again!
You can have him back.
We don't need him.
Kado!
Why, you?
Wait, who are these guys?
The bullies from the last island!
Kado never did anything to you!
Why did you have to do this to him?
You're right.
We had no need to retaliate
against your ugly bird.
But we needed to get our hands on that
little straw-haired friend of yours, you see.
The plan was simple.
We wanted to lure you both
into the jungle by having
your dear birdie here
squawk pitifully for help.
But the idiot refused to cooperate.
Now, you just call out
for your own opium now.
Give us a really loud squawk
and we might even let you go.
Alright, then we'll make you squawk.
Just call for the princess.
Call for help now!
Let's hear it, bird!
Call out to your beloved
princess, and this will all end!
Just open your mouth, you damn creature!
But then we realized
that little Straw Hat was
already neatly trapped
here just waiting for us.
In which case, we didn't
need that thing anymore.
Karoo?
What a dumb bird!
I'll kill you!
And were you the ones who planted
a bomb to injure the giant Dory?
Yeah, that's us.
Who is this new guy?
Is he on the list?
No, but he's clearly a friend of theirs.
Let's just get rid of him.
How dare you interfere
with a proud warrior duel!
It was you!
I'll kick your asses!
How about I get rid of you instead?
Oh, it's just so cute when
you find Miss Wednesday.
What's more, she really thinks she
stands a chance against agents like us!
Taste my peacock slasher!
I'll get you too!
Exploding Star!
Yeah, gotcha!
Wrong!
Nose fence and cannon!
Did you get burned? Usa!
10,000 kilograms? Press!
Now, now.
Let's calm down.
There's no need to get so
upset right now, Princess.
We aren't planning to kill you yet.
We only came here to abduct you.
Those were Mr.
Three's explicit orders.
Mr. Three?
The Wax Wax Fruit Man?
He's here on the island
with us! That's right. Mr.
Three the Candleman.
His body creates wax which he
can then control as he likes.
What's going on here?
Tell me!
Going on?
Of course it's lost on someone like you.
What's going on is that I'm creating
a work of art with your assistance.
Stand still like a good little girl.
Did you actually think
that someone like you could
escape from an organization
like Baroque Works?
After all,
your friend over there has a big bounty on
his head and look at what happened to him.
Ha.
Consider this our thank you for
what happened at Whiskey Peak.
You should learn to mind your own business,
you pathetic group of wannabe pirates.
It would be quite
beneficial to your health.
By the way, we have your swordsman friend.
And we've captured the other girl that
you brought along with you as well.
So you caught Zoro? Damn right.
In that case, you're in
more trouble than I thought.
Well, let's see how big you talk.
After one of my kicky bombs blows
up their little face of yours.
Try whatever tricks you want.
I'm gonna kick your ass.
This should be fun.
Mufi, no!
You weak little fool. Luffy!
No! Please! Luffy!
Let's go, Miss Valentine.
Usopp!
Cut out!
Damn you!
Struggling is pointless.
Once my candle jacket
solidifies around you,
it'll become as hard as iron and
it's impossible to break through.
There's no denying that
you giants are very strong.
But once you've been captured, that
strength doesn't do you any good at all.
None.
All that I had to do was use my brain.
There would be no sense in trying
to defeat you in a physical fight.
You were so busy enjoying your great win.
The capturing you is easy.
Don't glare at me like that.
It's positively terrifying.
You should be celebrating, shouldn't you?
At long last, your battle with Dory
the Blue Ogre has come to an end.
You fought on this island for a
hundred years for your precious pride.
Shouldn't such a long-lasting battle
make victory all the more sweet?
I mean, really, it's an accomplishment.
Even if it required a little outside help.
Come on, give me a little smile. Shut up!
What would you know about this?
Of course, the real victor
in all of this is me.
The bounties placed on your heads
long ago remain in place to this day.
Today you're worth 200 million berries.
Quite a handsome son.
Bounties?
Big bounties.
I feel as if I've uncovered
a long-lost treasure.
so that's what you're after here mr.
three here's the girl
alabaster's sneaky spy
it's about time I was
positively sick of waiting.
You're full of nothing but dirty tricks.
I can't believe you!
Putting a bomb in Dory's
alcohol was low even for you.
What the barrels!
You did something to the
The drinks that I gave Dory?
Dory, how was your drink?
Hit the spot, didn't it?
Yes, it tasted almost godly, in fact.
No, that must be what Dory meant.
Hmm, you're an annoying little girl,
Princess, giving away our secrets like that.
But that's all right.
There isn't anything he can
do about it now, anyway.
CANDLE!
Mr.
Five, bring the swordsman
and the other girl.
Time to begin.
GIANT CANDLE!
What is that thing?
Here are the others.
It's just sad.
Idiots like these should have
been a lot easier for me to catch.
Should have caught them the first time.
How embarrassing.
What is that thing? Nothing good.
I'm sorry, you guys.
But, Phoebe, what happened?
I thought you were with Luffy.
I was, but now...
If you're wondering about the straw
hat, I saw to that little runt myself.
Well, he didn't put up
much of a fight, either.
Right.
Welcome, one and all, to my
famous candle service set!
I guess this is what it feels like, to
be a candle stuck on a birthday cake.
Guys, what's that spinning up there?
I can't move. Great.
It's not surprising to me that
they don't want us moving around.
It's what captured means.
Damn, that stuff's hard.
And I can't put much strength
behind my swing from this angle.
Something's falling.
I do hope you enjoy my candle service.
You may have noticed the wax
flakes that are falling from above.
You'll eventually be covered
and turned into wax figures.
You'll become perfectly lifelike
statues for my collection.
Something that even I
couldn't achieve on my own.
I will literally capture your spirits
and encase them forever in wax shells.
It will be a true masterpiece.
You will die for my art.
I don't think so, you freak!
I have no interest in dying for
whatever it is you consider art!
Hey, giant!
Why are you laying there
doing nothing when you
could be beating the crap
out of this candle guy?
Now he is going to make one huge statue.
You can try to convince him, but
your efforts will be useless.
He's a little blue at the moment.
You see,
he just realized how
unfairly he won his last
fight and he's lost
the heart to celebrate.
He killed his dear friend Dory with
whom he had fought for 100 years.
Dory was injured, but he didn't notice.
Just imagine how much pain
Dory must have been in.
He didn't stand a chance.
You did shed a few tears, though.
Perhaps you were crying for your friend.
Now it's no use.
There's no one doing it.
He's dead, and it's all your fault.
I should have seen it. Huh?
I knew something strange was going on.
From the moment we first began to
fight, I knew Dory was hiding something?
but I couldn't tell what it was.
Hmm?
You say that you knew it.
You're lying!
If you knew something was wrong,
why didn't you stop the fight?
Why didn't you give him a chance to rest?
I didn't see one tread of pity in
the way you ruthlessly cut him down.
You know nothing about honorable duels.
Someone like you could
never understand my tears!
What do you know about the way of Elbath?
You think that I would shame a warrior?
Who hid the fact that he was weakened
so that he could continue to fight?
Only a truly great
warrior would go to such
lengths and such a man
isn't interested in pity.
Now, I know what really happened
and I must do something about it.
I'm going to finish this
with my own two hands.
That's the least I can do for Dory.
He was a great warrior and my dear friend.
Froggy!
This chatterin' was gettin' on my nerves.
Usopp. Usopp.
They have to pay for this.
Oh, yeah.
Those jerks have to pay.
You can't...take this either!
Alright, then it's settled!
Let's go beat them senseless!
Froggy!
Big fool!
It seems that I miscalculated.
I forgot how freakishly strong
these dumb giants can be.
It looks like you're going to
require more complete restraint.
Works, works!
Handcuffs!
Still going!
And now for the finishing touch.
Take this!
It'll be tough for you
to move now, won't it?
You really are despicable!
Now, let's get these candles going faster!
It's time to turn these people into
beautiful, artistic wax statues!
My chest is starting to hurt.
The wax is starting to get into our lungs.
At this rate, he's gonna turn
us into wax from the inside out.
That's it.
Make it look like you're in
as much pain as possible.
That's perfect!
Expressions of agony are what
I seek to achieve in my art.
The finished product
will be simply splendid!
You must die filled with terror!
This is what you call art, you
creaky, weird-haired freak!
You guys are gonna regret this!
You're gonna pay for what you did to Brook
and Dory and for what
you're trying to do to us!
You can yell and scream all
you want to, little girl!
No one can help you now!
A century.
For 100 years, Dory and I dueled day
in and day out, fighting endlessly.
We battled for our pride, as is
the way of the warriors of Elbath.
We fought with honor and with strength,
and still we are subjected to this!
Why has this happened to us?
Must we be forced to meet
our end in such a way?
Must we?
It isn't fair for a warrior to
die such a dishonorable death!
Why can I not die in battle?
Hold that look.
Yes, that's it.
Such grief, such sorrow, and
just the right amount of anger.
How marvelous.
Elbath, please.
This isn't good.
My hands won't move.
Can't we do something?
I don't want to die like this.
My body's already beginning to turn stiff.
What are we supposed to do?
Zoro, do something.
Hey, Giant.
You can still move, right?
Good. So can I.
I say we take them down together.
What do you think?
Hold on a second.
What are you doing?
Are you? Yeah. Quit messing around.
You're not going to cut your own legs off.
I'm not messing around at all.
It's the only way to get
us out of this situation.
Are you in or out?
Are you insane? No way!
Even if you get down from here,
you won't get far without legs.
There's no way to know
for sure until we try.
So are you saying you'd
rather just sit here and die?
Why should we make it easy
for those guys to kill us?
Dying quietly without a struggle
doesn't make you any less dead, right?
The girl was right.
This guy's insane.
He's bluffing.
There's no way he would do
something as crazy as that.
He's just trying to act tough
so his friends will feel better.
That runt's got spirit.
I'll give him that.
He's doing better than I am.
I had actually begun to
lose the will to fight.
Alright, I'm in.
Let's cut them to pieces.
You're not serious about this, are you?
How are you planning on
fighting them afterward?
Who knows? But...
I plan to win.
Who are these people?
They're completely nuts.
What kind of man is he, and why?
Why do I feel like I've seen
that look somewhere before?
Princess Vivi, sometimes it takes
more strength to live than to die.
Wait, I'll fight with you.
What?
Good, get ready.
And now, let's go!
Don't be foolish, what did
you want to accomplish?
When I get back, I'm
going to kick your ass in!
Let's get him, Usopp! Yeah!
The first guy!
Loopy! Usopp! Kado!
We're here, Froggy.
Don't worry, we'll pick
up where you left off.
Thanks, Usopp.
Beat them beyond recognition.
Show them expressions of pain
and agony they won't soon forget.
Oh, I'm good.
These guys messed up the best duel ever.
They're in some serious trouble
and they're gonna answer to me.
So you're the one with the
highest bounty in the East Blue?
My, how low marine standards have fallen.
It's almost tragic, really.
Is that your hair?
You just shut up!
Dude, it's on fire! Hush, you!
Yes, he has weird hair.
Now, could you break this pillar?
We're about to turn into wax statues here!
Oh, are you guys in trouble?
Nope, no trouble at all.
Wait, Zoro, your leg!
Yeah, I made it about
halfway through, I'd say.
And how exactly is that?
No trouble at all!
So, Luffy, what do you think?
Could you go ahead and take
care of this pillar for us?
I think I've done enough.
Yeah, no problem.
Ha!
I wouldn't be so sure.
I don't know what it
is, but let's break it.
Right, let's do it!
Usopp, the brave warrior of
the sea, is ready to fight!
Hurry, will ya?
We're dying here!
Tries to be fast from leaving home.
The factor behind our
back just keeps us strong.
It's too bad cause
we're still selling for?
It's so fun for ya!
Just leave us alone.
It may be for this
chasing impossible things.
But I just gotta try.
The crazier the dream!
The more ambition I'm gonna need.
It may be for this driving home.
But I know that I've just gotta fly!
Far through the sea,
the great of paradise.
We've gotta fly!
Don't give up, just keep on trying.
And you'll see that you're closer to?
The horizon of your dreams.